

KEY ACCOUNT CONSULTANT

- 9558168533
- <u>avdhip@gmail.com</u>
- Ahmedabad/ Gujarat/ India
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/avadhi-p-1402b6a0/

ABOUT ME

Passionate marketing professional with 2.3+ years of experience of sales and managing key accounts in well-known fin tech company. Effective communication skills, highly organised and persistent, determined with positive attitude are the skills I possess.

A compulsive to do list maker who really enjoy watching sitcoms and enthused by travelling. Seeking to gain maximum experience with numerous learning opportunities and secure progressing career opportunity to fully utilize my skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

SKILLS

- Account management
- Customer Relationship management
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving

EDUCATION

PGDM – Marketing & International Business

St. Kabir Institute of Professional Studies 2018 - 2020

BBA - Finance

Swami Sahajhanand College of Commerce and Management

2015 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

Key Account Consultant

PhonePe Pvt. Ltd./ Ahmedabad/ Jan 2022- Present (5 months)

Developed in depth understanding and managing of Key Accounts of different industry verticals like F&B, Healthcare and Wellness, Hospitality, Lifestyle, FMCG, etc.

- Adding new key accounts to the network, also to nurture and grow them
- Ensuring an increase in the market share of PhonePe in offline business
- Revenue generation through multiple products launched

Key Account Executive

PhonePe Pvt. Ltd./ Ahmedabad/ Feb 2020- Dec 2021 (1 year 10 months)

Acquiring key merchants and managing the accounts. Developing and maintaining amicable long-term relationships with merchants.

- Merchant Acquisition Acquiring new premium merchants
- Account Management Managing accounts and building relationships
- Mapping Competition and revenue generation

Internship

Khimji Ramdas India Pvt. Ltd./ Ahmedabad/ May 2019- July 2019 (2 months)

Product demonstration and B₂B selling of a newly launched product. Research on the customer service level of P&G products distribution by Khimji Ramdas and communication with sales, product and finance department.